

PAWEŁ LISZEWSKI

ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Paweł Liszewski. I am a Frontend Developer in the making. My goal is to continiously expand my skill set and gather new experience. I am a creative person who enjoys solving problems. I am grat at communicating and working in international teams. While coding I primarly focus on writing clean and efficient code. I am proficient in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript (ES5 and ES6) and React. I have working knowledge of jQuery, Bootstrap, Ajax, SASS, I am also familiar with Responsive Web Design and Object Oriented Programming. I can use Git version control system and Jira.

PERSONAL INFO ,

Date of birth 28/05/1992

Address: Madalińskiego 99A / 39 02-549 Warszawa

Phone number: 793 728 938

E-mail:

pawei.iiszewski.maii@gmaii.com

Portfolio

pawelliszewski92.github.io/portfolio/ index.html

SKILLS: /

- O HTML5
- O CSS3
- Javascript (ES5 and ES6)
- React
- o jQuery
- Ajax
- Bootstrap
- SASS
- Wordpress

- Object Oriented Programming
- Responsive Web Design
- O Git
- o Jira
- Adobe Photoshop and Inkscape basics
- MS Office, Google Docs
- University of Warsaw English Language Certificate - level B2

WORK EXPERIENCE: /

1.11.2017 - 31.07.2018

- People Can Fly sp. z o.o. Assistant Producer
 - managing work of international team
 - creating daily, weekly and monthly reports
 - setting new goals and tasks for the team
 - controlling project progress in Jira software
 - email and personal contracts with international publishers

2014 - now

- -- Agencja Bezpieczeństwa Biznesu SaLuS sp. z o.o.
 - polish-english translations
 - foreign customer relations
 - conducting correspondence

30.06.2014 - 30.07.2014

- ○ WYG Consulting sp. z o.o.
 - archiving documents
 - office administration

1.06.2011 - 31.07.2011

- "Grosik-Taxi" Andrzej Gajowniczek
 - call center customer service

EDUCATION:

24.02.2018 - 21.04.2018

--- Akademia108: Frontend Developer Coding Bootcamp

2015-2017

University of Warsaw: Master Management Studies Specialty: Marketing

2011-2015

Uniwersity of Warsaw: Bachelor Management Studies

2008-2011

The tenth Królowa Jadwiga Secondary Grammar School in Warsaw

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.